[{"answer": " Hello", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Hi, Gretchen.  Its me", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Hello", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Hey, Dave.  Hows it going", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Hi, Gretchen.  Its me", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Everythings good.  How about you", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Hey, Dave.  Hows it going", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Things here are good too.  Busy, but good.  So, hows the university pla", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Everythings good.  How about you", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Yeah, I think so.  Ive been looking online at different schools and looking up ho", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Things here are good too.  Busy, but good.  So, hows the university pla", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Did you find a lot of useful information", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Yeah, I think so.  Ive been looking online at different schools and looking up ho", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Yeah, I did.  I saw what was needed to apply for each school, but Im a littl", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Did you find a lot of useful information", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  Grad school can be really pricey.  Have you thought abou", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Yeah, I did.  I saw what was needed to apply for each school, but Im a littl", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " What kind of financial aid is available", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Oh, yeah.  Grad school can be really pricey.  Have you thought abou", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Well, there are basically two kinds: scholarships and assistantships", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 41, "question": " What kind of financial aid is available", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Which is better?  Im not really even sure what the difference is", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Well, there are basically two kinds: scholarships and assistantships", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " OK.  Scholarships are basically just money that is given to you to pay fo", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Which is better?  Im not really even sure what the difference is", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " That sounds pretty cool", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 47, "question": " OK.  Scholarships are basically just money that is given to you to pay fo", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Yeah.  If you can get one, its great, but its really hard for internationa", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 48, "question": " That sounds pretty cool", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Thats too bad", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Yeah.  If you can get one, its great, but its really hard for internationa", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " I know.  But assistantships are a good option", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Thats too bad", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Whats different with those", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 55, "question": " I know.  But assistantships are a good option", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " With assistantships you get tuition assistance.  So they pay part or all of you", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Whats different with those", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " That sounds like a pretty good deal", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 60, "question": " With assistantships you get tuition assistance.  So they pay part or all of you", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Yeah, it is.  But, you do have to work for them during the school year an", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 61, "question": " That sounds like a pretty good deal", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Yeah, it is.  But, you do have to work for them during the school year an", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Yeah.  They have TAs, which are teaching assistantships.  With those yo", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Oh, I would hate to teach.  Is that the only kind", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Yeah.  They have TAs, which are teaching assistantships.  With those yo", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " No, theres also RAs and GAs.  RAs are research assistantships.  For thi", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Oh, I would hate to teach.  Is that the only kind", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Mmmhmmm", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 80, "question": " No, theres also RAs and GAs.  RAs are research assistantships.  For thi", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " GA stands for graduate assistantship.  For a GA, you usually help out ", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Mmmhmmm", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " It sounds like there are a few options then", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 86, "question": " GA stands for graduate assistantship.  For a GA, you usually help out ", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " There are.  You should apply for one", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 87, "question": " It sounds like there are a few options then", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " How do I find out about assistantships at the different universities", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 88, "question": " There are.  You should apply for one", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " You can check with the Financial Aid Office or in the specific departmen", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 89, "question": " How do I find out about assistantships at the different universities", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " OK, Ill do that", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 94, "question": " You can check with the Financial Aid Office or in the specific departmen", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Call me back later and let me know what you find", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 95, "question": " OK, Ill do that", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " OK, I will.  Thanks.  Bye", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 96, "question": " Call me back later and let me know what you find", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": "Bye", "docId": "06-02", "aSentId": 97, "question": " OK, I will.  Thanks.  Bye", "qSentId": 96}]
